Inventory to the James B. Webster papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Incremental materials, 1902-2003
  - Diplomas of Alta Newby and James B. Webster, 1906-1908 (Box 39)
  - Photographs and photo albums
    - "Scenes from Chinese life" (Box 40)
    - "Kuling" (Box 40)
    - "Scenery" (Box 40)
    - "Honolulu and other places" (Box 40)
    - James B. Webster and Alta Newby family photos, 1907-1908 (Box 41)
    - Mission work in China, circa 1911 (Box 41)
    - Negatives of family photographs, Sunday school, Alta Newby before and after her wedding, and others (Box 42)
  - Conference on Religious Education, Shanghai College, program and publications, circa 1923 (Box 42)
  - "Student Ministry to Children: Manual for Teachers in Daily Vacation Bible Schools,", 1919 (Box 42)
  - Outlines for Mothers' Meetings, 1924 (Box 42)
  - Conference of Christian Colleges and Universities, Nanking, notes, programs, and other materials, 1924 February (Box 42)
  - Photographs of mission work in Nanchang and Shanghai, 1903-1920 (Box 43)
  - "Industrial and Natural Resources in China," hand drawn map with samples of resources glued to corresponding region, undated (Box 44)
  - Hand painted Chinese poster, undated (Box 44)
  - Cartoon sketches and statistical figures related to education in China, undated (Box 44)
  - Black and white panoramic photograph of Shanghai College graduates, classes 1923-1928, with James B. Webster at the center, circa 1928 (Map case case)
  - Ink drawing by Walter G. Yip depicting an education race, with China and the Middle East in last place and the United States crossing the finish line, 1919 (Map case case)